{
  "grammarQuestions": [{
      "grammarQuestion": "Do you like apples?",
      "grammarTaskFrom": "?+",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".+",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "Yes, I do. I like apples.",
        "Yes, I don't. I like apples.",
        "Yes, I am. I like apples.",
        "No, I do. I don't like apples."
      ],
      "correct": "Yes, I do. I like apples."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "Do you like melons?",
      "grammarTaskFrom": "?+",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".+",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "Yes, I do. I like melons.",
        "Yes, I am. I like melon.",
        "Yes, I do. I like melones.",
        "Yes, I do. I don't like watermelons."
      ],
      "correct": "Yes, I do. I like melons."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "Do you like pineapples?",
      "grammarTaskFrom": "?+",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".-",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "No, I don't. I don't like pineapples.",
        "No, I don't. I dont like pineapples.",
        "No, I do. I don't like pineapples.",
        "No, I'm not. I don't like pineapple."
      ],
      "correct": "No, I don't. I don't like pineapples."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "Do you like pears?",
      "grammarTaskFrom": "?+",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".-",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "No, I don't. I don't like pears.",
        "Yes, I am. I like pear.",
        "Yes, I am. I like pears.",
        "No, I'm not. I don't like pears."
      ],
      "correct": "No, I don't. I don't like pears."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "Do you like bananas?",
      "grammarTaskFrom": "?+",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".+",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "Yes, I do. Bananas are yummy.",
        "No, I don't. Bananas are yummy.",
        "Yes, I do. Bananas is yucky.",
        "No, I don't. Banana are yucky."
      ],
      "correct": "Yes, I do. Bananas are yummy."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "What do you want to be?",
      "grammarTaskFrom": "?+",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "I wanted to be a teacher.",
        "I want a teacher.",
        "I want to be a teacher.",
        "I want be a teacher."
      ],
      "correct": "I want to be a teacher."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "I want to be a nurse.",
      "grammarTaskFrom": ".",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".+",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "Yes, I want to be a nurse.",
        "Yes, I be a nurse",
        "Yes, don't. I want to be a teacher.",
        "Yes, I do. I want to be a nurse."
      ],
      "correct": "Yes, I do. I want to be a nurse."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "No, I don't. I don't want to be a doctor",
      "grammarTaskFrom": ".-",
      "grammarTaskTo": "?+",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "Do I want to be a doctor?",
        "Do I want be a doctor?",
        "Don't I want to be a doctor?",
        "Yes, I do. I want to be a doctor."
      ],
      "correct": "Do I want to be a doctor?"
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "I don't want to be a singer",
      "grammarTaskFrom": ".",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".-",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "No, I do. I dont want to be singer.",
        "No, I don't. I don't want to be a singer.",
        "Don't I want to be a singer?",
        "No, I did. I didn't want to be a singer."
      ],
      "correct": "No, I don't. I don't want to be a singer."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "Do you like dogs?",
      "grammarTaskFrom": "?+",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".+",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "Yes, I do. I like dogs.",
        "Yes, I don't. I like dogs.",
        "I like dogs.",
        "Yes, I do. I like dog."
      ],
      "correct": "Yes, I do. I like dogs."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "Yes, I do. I like turtles.",
      "grammarTaskFrom": ".+",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".-",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "No, I don't. I don't like dogs.",
        "No, I don't. I don't like turtles.",
        "No, I do. I don't like turtles",
        "No, I doesn't. I doesn't like turtles."
      ],
      "correct": "No, I don't. I don't like turtles."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "She likes lions.",
      "grammarTaskFrom": ".+",
      "grammarTaskTo": "?+",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "Does she likes lions?",
        "Does she like lions?",
        "Do she like lions?",
        "Does she like lion?"
      ],
      "correct": "Does she like lions."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "Does she like rabbits?",
      "grammarTaskFrom": "?+",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".-",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "No, she doesn't. She doesn't like rabbits.",
        "No, she doesn't She doesn't like rabbit.",
        "No, she don't. She don't like rabbits.",
        "No, she does. She doesn't lie rabbits."
      ],
      "correct": "No, she doesn't. She doesn't like rabbits."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "Yes, she does. She likes tigers.",
      "grammarTaskFrom": ".+",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".-",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "No, she doesn't. She doesn't like tigers.",
        "No, she does. She does not like tigers.",
        "No, she don't. She don't like tigers.",
        "No, she does. She does like tigers."
      ],
      "correct": "No, she doesn't. She doesn't like tigers."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "He doesn't like birds.",
      "grammarTaskFrom": ".",
      "grammarTaskTo": "?+",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "Does he likes birds?",
        "Does he like birds?",
        "Do he likes birds?",
        "Do he like bird?"
      ],
      "correct": "Does he like birds."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "Yes, they do. They like to play football.",
      "grammarTaskFrom": ".+",
      "grammarTaskTo": "?+",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "Do they like to play football?",
        "Do they like play football?",
        "Does they like to play football?",
        "Doesn't the like to play football?"
      ],
      "correct": "Do they like to play football."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "Does he like to play soccer?",
      "grammarTaskFrom": "?+",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".+",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "Yes, he does. He likes to play soccer.",
        "Yes, he do. He likes to play football.",
        "Yes, he does. He likes play soccer.",
        "Yes, he does. He like to play football."
      ],
      "correct": "Yes, he does. He likes to play soccer."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "Do we like cherries?",
      "grammarTaskFrom": "?+",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".-",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "No, we doesn't. We don't like tigers.",
        "No, we don't. We don't like cherries.",
        "No, we don't. We don't like cherry.",
        "No, we do. We like cherries."
      ],
      "correct": "No, we don't. We don't like cherries."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "Yes, they do. They like to play basketball.",
      "grammarTaskFrom": ".+",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".-",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "No, they don't. They don't like to play basketball.",
        "No, they doesn't. They doesn't like to play basketball.",
        "No, they don't. They don't like play basketball.",
        "No, they do. They don't like to play basketball"
      ],
      "correct": "No, they don't. They don't like to play basketball."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "He likes to play tennis.",
      "grammarTaskFrom": ".",
      "grammarTaskTo": "?+",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "Does he like to play tennis?",
        "Do he like to play tennis?",
        "Does he like play tennis?",
        "Does he likes to play tennis?"
      ],
      "correct": "Does he like to play tennis."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "We like strawberries.",
      "grammarTaskFrom": ".",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".-",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "No we don't. We don't like strawberries.",
        "No, we do. We do like strawberries.",
        "No we don't. We don't like strawberry.",
        "No, we not. We don't like strawberries."
      ],
      "correct": "No we don't. We don't like strawberries."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "What color is your hair?",
      "grammarTaskFrom": "?+",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "It's white.",
        "Its white.",
        "It's a white.",
        "Its white."
      ],
      "correct": "It's white."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "What color are your eyes?",
      "grammarTaskFrom": "?+",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "It's blue.",
        "They blue.",
        "They're blue.",
        "They're blues."
      ],
      "correct": "They're blue."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "Are his eyes brown?",
      "grammarTaskFrom": "?+",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".+",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "Yes, they are.",
        "Yes, they brown.",
        "Yes, they aren't.",
        "Yes, they."
      ],
      "correct": "Yes, they are."
    }, {
      "grammarQuestion": "Are your hair short?",
      "grammarTaskFrom": "?+",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".-",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "No, it isn't. It's long.",
        "No, it is. It's long.",
        "No, It not. It's long.",
        "No, its not. It's long."
      ],
      "correct": "No, it isn't. It's long."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "Do you have 2 heads?",
      "grammarTaskFrom": "?+",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".-",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "No, I don't. I have 1 head.",
        "No, I do. I have 1 head.",
        "No, I'm not. I have 1 head.",
        "No, I don't. I don't have 1 head."
      ],
      "correct": "No, I don't. I have 1 head."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "Do you have 1 tummy?",
      "grammarTaskFrom": "?+",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".+",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "Yes, I do. I have 1 tummy.",
        "Yes, I don't. I have 1 tummy.",
        "Yes, I am. I have 1 tummy.",
        "Yes, I do. I have 1 tumy."
      ],
      "correct": "Yes, I do. I have 1 tummy."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "Do you have 2 arms?",
      "grammarTaskFrom": "?+",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".+",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "Yes, I do. I have 2 arms.",
        "Yes, I don't. I have 2 arms.",
        "Yes, I am. I have 2 arms.",
        "Yes, I do. I have 2 arm."
      ],
      "correct": "Yes, I do. I have 2 arms."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "I have 10 toes.",
      "grammarTaskFrom": ".",
      "grammarTaskTo": "?-",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "Don't I have 10 toes?",
        "Dont I have 10 toes?",
        "Am I have 10 toes?",
        "Do I have 10 toes?"
      ],
      "correct": "Don't I have 10 toes?"
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "You have 2 knees.",
      "grammarTaskFrom": ".",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".+",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "Yes, you do. You have 2 knees.",
        "Yes, you are. You have 2 knees.",
        "Yes, you does. You have 2 knees.",
        "Yes, you do. You has 2 knees."
      ],
      "correct": "Yes, you do. You have 2 knees."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "She has 2 knees.",
      "grammarTaskFrom": ".",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".+",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "Yes, she does. She has 2 knees.",
        "Yes, she do. She has 2 knees.",
        "Yes, she is. She has 2 knees.",
        "Yes, she does. She have 2 knees."
      ],
      "correct": "Yes, she does. She has 2 knees."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "She has 5 fingers.",
      "grammarTaskFrom": ".",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".-",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "No, she doesn't. She has 10 fingers.",
        "No, she does. She has 10 fingers.",
        "No, she don't. She have 10 fingers.",
        "No, she don't. She has 10 fingers."
      ],
      "correct": "No, she doesn't. She has 10 fingers."
    },
    {
      "grammarQuestion": "Does he have 1 foot.",
      "grammarTaskFrom": "?+",
      "grammarTaskTo": ".-",
      "grammarChoices": [
        "No, he doesn't. He has 2 feet.",
        "No, he doesn't. He has 2 foots.",
        "No, he does. He has 2 feet.",
        "No, he don't. He has 2 feet."
      ],
      "correct": "No, he doesn't. He has 2 feet."
    }

  ]
}